Warning
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not, under any circumstances,
imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First